Oh, Leonard, huge mistake.
(Howard:)There's a whole buffet of women out there
and you're just standing in the corner...
...eating the same deviled egg,
over and over again.
(Leonard:)At least I have an egg.
What do you have?
(Howard:)A veritable smorgasbord
of potential sexual partners.
See the blond over there?
(Howard:)I can hit on her and you can't.
(Leonard:)So go hit on her.
(Howard:)She's not my type.
(Raj:)Too bad.
She was checking you out before.
- She was?
- Of course not. Look at her.
You know, I don't care
what you guys think.
(Leonard:)Stephanie and I are very happy
living together.
I will give either of you $20 right now
to trade pants with me.
- Sheldon? What are you doing here?
- Hang on.